{
    "subject": "resource/James_Cronin",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Chicago,_Illinois",
    "human_readable": "James Cronin was born in Chicago, Illinois.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8935282230377197,
            "question": "Where was James Cronin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8690810203552246,
            "question": "What state was James Cronin born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5106785893440247,
            "question": "What is James Cronin known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39210256934165955,
            "question": "What field of study was James Cronin involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37795013189315796,
            "question": "How is James Cronin remembered today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3430078625679016,
            "question": "Where did James Cronin likely go to school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3224177360534668,
            "question": "Is there anything else notable about James Cronin's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.302897572517395,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about James Cronin's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27501344680786133,
            "question": "Did James Cronin receive any awards or recognitions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23689180612564087,
            "question": "What impact did James Cronin have on his field of study?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Cronin was born in Chicago, Illinois.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5747_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did James Cronin receive any awards or recognitions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5747_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about James Cronin's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5747_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else notable about James Cronin's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5747_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5747_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5747_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5747_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5747_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5747_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5747_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5747_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5747_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5747_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5747_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided in multiple documents that state James Cronin was born on September 29, 1931, in Chicago, IL."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}